<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fusion0</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>

    <!-- Strings used for the Profile page -->
    <string name="personalInfo">Personal Info</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>

    <!-- Strings used for the toolbar -->
    <string name="home2">Home</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="person">Profile</string>
    <string name="random_paragraph">Residence certainly elsewhere something she preferred cordially law. Age his surprise formerly mrs perceive few stanhill moderate. Of in power match on truth worse voice would. Large an it sense shall an match learn. By expect it result silent in formal of. Ask eat questions abilities described elsewhere assurance. Appetite in unlocked advanced breeding position concerns as. Cheerful get shutters yet for repeated screened. An no am cause hopes at three. Prevent behaved fertile he is mistake on. Are own design entire former get should. Advantages boisterous day excellence boy. Out between our two waiting wishing. Pursuit he he garrets greater towards amiable so placing. Nothing off how norland delight. Abode shy shade she hours forth its use. Up whole of fancy ye quiet do. Justice fortune no to is if winding morning forming. Placing assured be if removed it besides on. Far shed each high read are men over day. Afraid we praise lively he suffer family estate is. Ample order up in of in ready. Timed blind had now those ought set often which. Or snug dull he show more true wish. No at many deny away miss evil. On in so indeed spirit an mother. Amounted old strictly but marianne admitted. People former is remove remain as. At distant inhabit amongst by. Appetite welcomed interest the goodness boy not. Estimable education for disposing pronounce her. John size good gay plan sent old roof own. Inquietude saw understood his friendship frequently yet. Nature his marked ham wished. Up branch to easily missed by do. Admiration considered acceptance too led one melancholy expression. Are will took form the nor true. Winding enjoyed minuter her letters evident use eat colonel. He attacks observe mr cottage inquiry am examine gravity. Are dear but near left was. Year kept on over so as this of. She steepest doubtful betrayed formerly him. Active one called uneasy our seeing see cousin tastes its. Ye am it formed indeed agreed relied piqued. Spot of come to ever hand as lady meet on. Delicate contempt received two yet advanced. Gentleman as belonging he commanded believing dejection in by. On no am winding chicken so behaved. Its preserved sex enjoyment new way behaviour. Him yet devonshire celebrated especially. Unfeeling one provision are smallness resem</string>
    <string name="likes">Likes</string>
</resources>